Narrator: 1
Speaker: What did I do so bad in this world that I deserve this?
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Every time one of the guard would ask me anything, I’d just get a pencil out,
or a pen or, whatever I had, and write my response.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: I sit back on that little small bed and that’s when I thanked God that my mother was still alive, …
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Two little kids that just, our mothers told us to go out and play,
and our friendship have lasted for 59 years and Lester and I don’t agree on everything,
but Lester and I have a bond that is unbreakable.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: And all the young men that was around me saw that I was crying …
Narrator: 6
Speaker: I said,
‘You telling me that we don’t have to stop at the filling station and ask for directions no more?’